And now we continue with the L Shape Traveling Walk with the stretch on the ends.
So let's start out on the right foot.
We take three steps forward and then we pause on that right foot and left foot goes up and we stretch.
We walk back, balancing on the left foot, we stretch.
We walk to the right, step touch step and we stretch.
We walk to the left and we stretch.
And then we walk back forward and we stretch.
And then that stretch freely lets your body yawn and open.
Walk, step touch step, stretch.
Step touch step, open.
So imagine like moving from the inside out like a star.
You're the star from the inside out.
Letting the movement radiate from the center, from your core as you stretch out, reach out.
Enjoy the stretch.
Traveling Step L Shape Stretch.